leprix.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Leprix

## INTRODUCTION

LePrix provides an online marketplace for users to shop authentic pre-owned and new clothing, accessories, shoes, handbags, jewelry, home goods, and technology accessories from pre-approved list of secondhand or resale businesses who list and sell their items. LePrix is a SnobSwap Inc. company.

This is LePrix's Privacy Policy. We respect your privacy and we appreciate your trust in us to secure your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the extent of and limitations on how we collect, use, and disclose your personal information. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and feel free to email Contact Us if you have any question.

## OVERVIEW

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.LePrix.com and mobile applications (the "Site" or "Services") and apply generally to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on May 15, 2013 for all users. The term "user(s)" and "member(s)" are used interchangeably.

## 18 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

In collecting personal information, we strive to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and more convenient. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, shipping information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use the service or feature.

Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, such as, but not limited to: if you are registering using an email account at a free email service, or registering to swap, sell, or buy on the Site. We use your financial information, including credit card information to verify the accuracy of your name, address, and other information.

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. (Learn more about why we use cookies). Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

If you choose to use the Site, we collect information about usage behavior. We also collect other members' comments about you in our review pages.

If you establish a credit card account (including PayPal and Affirm) with us to pay for certain services or to verify your address, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date. Credit card information is stored securely with our payment processing partner Stripe.

If you choose to post messages in our, community forums, member reviews, groups or other message areas or leave reviews for other members, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other members or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

If you register for LePrix on another web site or use a web site providing a service for LePrix or a web site that helps facilitate your activity on LePrix, that web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to LePrix.

If you use certain features of the Services, including the mobile applications, LePrix may receive, store and process different types of information about your location, including general information (e.g., IP Address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based functionality). If access the Services through mobile device and you do not want location-traction information shared, you can disabled the GPS or location-tracking functions as long as your device allows it.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request, in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User Names or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

If you choose to list an item for sale or purchase on the Site or open a credit account, or otherwise provide us with your financial information, we use your address and billing information to bill you, verify your address and provide associated support.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Services usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Services' content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Services and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on the "Manage My Account" page. Contact Us to change your notification preferences at any time.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you are granting us permission to display it to visitors of the web site. If you supply a LePrix member with your postal address you are granting them permission to use it to contact you and/or send correspondence.

To unsubscribe, please contact us at contact@LePrix.com

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal course of business to provide our services.

#### Advertisers

We gather personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. In other words, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your consent.

#### User Name

Your User Name is displayed throughout the Site and is therefore available to the public. All of your activities on the Site will be identifiable to your User Name. Other people can see the items you are offering to sell and items that you want, items that you have purchased in the past, your feedback or review rating and associated comments, your postings on the Site, and so on. Therefore, if you associate your name with your User Name, the people you have revealed your name to will be able to personally identify your LePrix activities. Although our pages are coded with robot exclusion headers, others may illegally attempt to automatically collect your email address from the Site. We describe how to change your email and User Name below. If you are involved in a transaction, we have features that allow other members to view your email address and obtain your contact and shipping information to help complete the transaction. Further, we may send out notices to you or other members regarding suspicious activity or policy violations on the Site.

#### Third Party Service Providers

We may use third parties service providers ("service providers") to facilitate one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these service providers. These service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced LePrix related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the service provider may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to a service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.

#### Business Transfers

In event of a corporate merger, reorganization, dissolution, selling of assets or business, or similar events, personal information may be transferred as part of assets.

#### Legal Requests

LePrix cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the LePrix community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, User Name history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

## USING OTHER MEMBERS' PERSONAL INFORMATION

In order to facilitate interaction among all LePrix members, our Site allows you limited access other members' contact and shipping information. As a member you have access to the User Name, email address and other contact and shipping information of the other members involved in the transaction. By entering into our Terms of Use, you agree that, with respect to other members' personal information that you obtain through the Site or through an LePrix-related communication or LePrix-facilitated transaction, LePrix hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) LePrix-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, (b) any other purpose that a user expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use it for. In all cases, you must give members an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, can you disclose personal information about another user to any third party without our express, written consent and the consent of that user. You agree that other members may use your personal information to communicate with you in accordance with this Section. Note that law enforcement personnel and other rights holders are given different rights with respect to information they access.

## USE OF EMAIL TOOLS

You may not use the email of LePrix members other than for the intended purpose of communicating about items listed on the Site. You may not give other members' email addresses to any third-party service including other email services would send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our Terms of Use. We do not permanently store email messages or the email addresses sent from these tools. If you send, message, and email using the Refer a Friend or Share function to show another person an item listed on the Site to an email address that is not registered in our community, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than to send your email. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

## YOUR PASSWORD

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User Name and password, including fees charged to your account. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your LePrix password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User Name and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

## ACCESSING AND EDITING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We offer you the ability to automatically review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the Site and entering in the new information yourself. Generally, we will not modify your personal information based on your request because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. You can change your user Id, email address, contact information, financial information, shipping information and user preferences by going to the necessary section in account info tab of your profile page. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once posted, you may not be able to change or remove any public postings made on the Site including our chat rooms or other message areas or the feedback area Upon your request, we will deactivate your account, contact information, billing information, shipping information, and financial information from our active databases. To make this request, Contact Us. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. We will retain in our files some personal information you have requested to remove to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will be deactivated from public and member viewing and will only be available to select LePrix personnel.

LePrix does not knowingly collection personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you are not allowed to use the Services so please do not submit any personal information through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet and mobile device usage. If you have reason to believe that a child under 13 years of age has provided Personal Data, please email us at contact@LePrix.com so that we can delete that information.

## OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties or fellow members, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since LePrix does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## SECURITY

Your information is stored on LePrix's servers located in the United States. We use industry-standard safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your personal information with encryption, firewalls, and secure socket layers. We consider data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. However, despite our best efforts to secure your personal information, as described in the Terms of Use, use of this Site is at your own risk. Unfortunately, there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet.

## EXCLUSIONS

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal information collected by LePrix other than personal information collected through the Services. The Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to LePrix through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums ("Public Areas") and any new ideas for new products or modifications to existing products and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and LePrix shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

## NOTICE

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site.

## GENERAL INFORMATION

If any provision of the Privacy Policy is deemed unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, such provision(s) will be deemed severable from the rest of the Terms and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the rest of the Terms. Failure of LePrix to exercise any rights or remedies will not constitute a waiver of any rights or remedies available to LePrix under these provisions or at law. These provisions represent the entire agreement between you and LePrix and supersede and replace any other agreement between the parties including but not limited to any previous Terms as they may have applied between you and LePrix. Paragraph headings are for convenience only and not for interpretation of these provisions.
